Now, short-form content is a lot easier.
Adam Sullivan, again, at the moment,
is just doing point and shoot.
He takes the phone out, presses plus.
"You'll never guess what, brother.
I just saw someone in a fucking Evidence
T-shirt, brother." And people are there
like, "Oh, amazing reel.
Fucking amazing reel." When people
are like, "I don't have
time to post on social media," you could
literally squat rack. "Hi, guys.
Just in case you weren't sure,
these J-hooks here,
if you get them at chest height,
it's going to be the most comfortable for
a back squat.
Just saw someone there, the J-hook
was too high,
they had to go on their tiptoes to
put the rack... Anyway,
if you have any questions about the squat
rack, just put
them in the comments
and I'll get back to you in a second."
Post.
You get one question,
you then reply to that question
and make a reel with the
questions in it.
"John here asks about this in the squat,"
ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
Is that reel going to get you millions of
views and tens of thousands of clients?
No. But it's easy to produce.
You just press a button on your phone,
you point and
shoot. You don't just grab your phone
and hold it sideways. "Welcome to YouTube.
Today..." It needs a bit more strategy.
Long-form is less forgiving,
because you can work on a long-form video
for
two weeks, and if it doesn't take off,
there's nothing you can do.
If YouTube decides not to put it in front
of people, YouTube's like, "See you."
That two weeks, gone. You, fucked.
Doesn't care.
For Instagram, you're like, "Oh, cool,
I'll just do another one later."